# **Christian Kane**

Texas A&M Computer Science Student

# **Personal Info**

**Email** 

christiankane@tamu.edu

**Phone** 

832-364-7271

**Address** 

11902 Foxburo Dr Houston, TX 77065

**GitHub** 

https://github.com/ChristianRossKane

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/christian-kane-845702177/

# **Skills**

Written and Verbal Communication

**Problem Solving** 

**Programming** 

Mathematics

Agile Methodologies

# Languages

C++	****
Python	****
Java	****
PSQL	****
Ruby	****
HTML/CSS	****

I managed to complete my entire degree in 3 years with an above average GPA; while this did not allow for me to gather much experience through internships, it is a testament to how truly willing I am to *learn and work with diligence* under difficult constraints.

# **Work History**

2021-08

**Peer Teacher** 

- 2022-01

Texas A&M University, College Station, TX

Helped facilitate labs for Programming classes that I had excelled in, alongside holding Office Hours for the majority of core Undergraduate Computer Science classes.

# **Education**

2019-08

Computer Science, Bachelor of Science

- 2022-05

Texas A&M University, College Station (GPA, 3.647)

**Mathematics, Minor** 

Texas A&M University, College Station

### Courses

2020-08

**Data Structures and Algorithms** 

Learned the fundamental data structures that underpin the majority of computing.

Grade Earned: A

2021-01

**Design and Analysis of Algorithms** 

Senior elective in which we analyized and applied some advanced modern algorithms in computing.

Grade Earned: A

2021-08

**Software Engineering** 

Senior elective in which the class environment was meant to emulate a true software developmental environment using Agile methodologies in which a product was developed for a real client. First exposure to Ruby on Rails and CI/CD development using GitHub and a Heroku Pipeline.

CI/CD development using Gitt lub and a Heroi

Project Worked on: <u>https://tx.ag/nickwork</u>

Grade Earned: A

2021-08

**Honors Computer and Network Security** 

Senior elective in which we learned the fundamental technologies and practices that go into protecting computers and wireless networks; applied and cracked cryptographic algorithms used today; learned about the security of modern cryprocurrencies and their respective blockchains.

Grade Earned: A